Guide to the Records of the Women's Philharmonic M1470
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series V: Development: Grants/Giving
  - Subseries VIII: Miscellaneous Grant/Fund files
    - Corporate Donor Research and Notes (Box 141, Folder 14)
    - Foundations, 2001 (Box 141, Folder 15)
    - Company Match (Box 141, Folder 17)
    - William and Flora Hewlett Foundation (Part 1) (Box 141, Folder 18)
    - Copland Music Fund, 03/2004 (Box 141, Folder 19)
    - Koret Foundation (Box 141, Folder 20)
    - Heller, 2003-2004 (Box 141, Folder 21)
    - Zeller Bach, 2003 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Alice M. Ditson Fund (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Virgil Thomson (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Strategic Issues and Funder Expectations Notes and Grants materials, 2003-2004 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Walter and Elise Haas Fund (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Gilmore Fund (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Nancy Pelosi: congratulatory letter re. NEA endowment, 2003 (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Misc. Funders, 2004 (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Audit Info for grants, 1999 (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - Accessing Arts Entrepreneurship: the Realities... (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Event Sponsorhip, 1998-1999 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Planned Giving, 1998/1999 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - 1998/99 Fundraising concerns, meetings and timelines (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Database: donors (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous grant proposal status and notes (1987-1997) (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Survey of Orchestras, 1998/1999 (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Membership survey, 1/1999 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Member survey, 1999 (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - Development (Box 150, Folder 17)
- Series VI: Press/Reviews
  Press and Reviews
  This includes newspapers, magazines and other publications that contained articles or reviews about the Women's Philharmonic.
  - Womens Philharmonic Press/Reviews: Ms Magazine August 2001 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - SF Examiner May 10, 2001 "Music to their Heirs" (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - SF Chronicle, May 9, 2001 "Daughter Rescues Mom's Music" (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - NY Times March 27, 2001 "Chen Yi" (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Symphony Magazine "Chen Yi" (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - SFCV Review sept. 29, 2001 "Melody of China" concert (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - SF Classical Voice May 13 2001 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - San Jose Mercury News May 10. 2001 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Contra Costa Times March 10, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Critical Response (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - SF Chronicle March 10, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - SF Classical Voice March 10, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Out Now Magazine March 10, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Contra Costa Times March 10, 2001 (feature) (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - San Jose Mercury News Sept. 2000 (feature) (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - SF Chronicle Critics Pick Sept 30 2000 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - SF Examiner Sept. 29 2000 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Top 10 Fall Classical Events 2000-01 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Contra Costa Times Sept. 30, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - San Francisco Classical Voice Sept. 30, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - SF Chronicle Sept. 30, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - San Jose Mercury News Sept. 30, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - SF Chronicle May 26, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - San Jose Mercury News March 25, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - San Francisco Classical Voice March 25, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - San Francisco Classical Voice May 26, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - SF Chronicle March 25, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Oakland Tribune 2/11/1998 WP Offers intriguing mix of gems (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - SF Frontiers January 16, 1997 "It's by women not just for..." (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Bay Times January 9 1997 "WP Rises Again" (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - SF Examiner January 1997 "On a Positive Note" (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Oakland Tribune January 4, 1997 "Concerted Effort" (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - San Jose Mercury News January 24 1997 "WP Rebounds" (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Paul Hertelendy Dec. 10, 1997 WP Director sees glass ceiling (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Misc. WP Mentions in Media; 1996-97 Season (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Radio Interview with Deutschland June 1996 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Chen Yi Press Clippings (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - China and World Cultural Exchange Press October 1996 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Bay Times June 26, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - SF Examiner June 14, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - New York Times June 8, 1996 "Finding her way..." (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - SF Chronicle June 18, 1996 "Chen Yi's Talent is no Myth" (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - East Bay papers June 13, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Bay Times June 13, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Chinese Media June 1996 Chen Yi (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - SF Chronicle June 1996 "Saturday Idyll" (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - SF Chronicle June 9, 1996 "Classical Convergence" (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - SF Examiner June 17, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Asian Week June 21, 1996 "Myths and Music" (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Myths and Poems press listings/clippings June 1996 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - In Galli Cantu Summer 1996 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - SF Chronicle 11/17/1997 WP Opener lackluster (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - San Jose Mercury News 11/17/1997 Thrilling Opener for WP (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Contra Costa Times 11/17/1997 New Leader Shapes Music Flawlessly (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - November 1998 press clippings (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Contra Costa Times 11/14/1997 New Conductor Debuts this Weekend (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Bay Area Business Woman 11/1997 The Women's Philharmonic starts New Season (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - San Jose Mercury News Advance 11/12/1997 Hsu Takes over (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - SF Examiner 11/11/1997 She's On a Musical Mission (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - San Mateo County Times 11/10/1997 Women's Phil has new conductor (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - World Journal 11/8/1997 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Oakland Tribune 11/1997 Hsu Makes auspicious debut (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Fall 1997 Misc. Clippings (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Press around 6/1997 Hsu appointment (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - World Journal 6/13/1997 Hsu Hire (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Contra Costa Times 6/1/1997 Composers orhestrate promotion (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Mercury News/Oakland Trib. 5/1997 Chen Yi CD (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - SF Chronicle 5/21/1997 Hsu to lead women's philharmonic (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - San Francisco Bay Gaurdian 4/23/1997 Women's Philharmonic and Chanticleer (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Bay Times 4/3/1997 Women's Phil. Ends with "Seasons" (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - SF Chronicle 3/18/1997 Letter to the Editor (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - The Washington Post Women composers unsung until now (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Bay Area Reporter 3/6/1998 Round Two (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - SF Chronicle 3/3/1997 Vivid postcards from Philharmonic (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Oakland Tribune 3/3/1997 Phil. offers adventurous program (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Concert Press Clippings 3/1/1997 Listings (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - 3/29/1997 Concert Press Clippings listings (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Concert Press Clippings January 23 1999 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - East Bay Papers 2/1997 "Bay Area Fosters..." "Bay Area like a bit of..." (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - 2/21/1997 Mills College Colloquium (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - City Search 2/1997 Top Pick (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Los Angeles Times: Womens Philharmonic has some scores to settle (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - SF Datebook 2/2/1997 Brilliant music from Chen Yi (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Datebook 1/19/1997 WP takes a new bow (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - SF Chronicle 1/27/1997 WP tunes up (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - 1/25/1997 Concert Press Clippings (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Bay Area Repertor 1/23/1997 Pit stop (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - East Bay Paper 1/21/1997 Pioneering ensemble (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - 1/1997 Womens Philharmonic Season (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - SJ Mercury 1/1997 Alternative (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - The Times 1/24/1997 Phil. tests drives conductor (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - SF Examiner 3/3/1997 WP: Premiers not original (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Joann Falletta Press (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - City Search "Movers and Shakers" interview with Apo Hsu (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Bay area Career Women Feb. 26 2000 concert (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Contra Costa Times Concert review October 16, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - San Francisco Classical Voice October 16, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - May 28, 1999 Concert Reviews (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - SF Weekly Mag. The Best of 1999 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Bay Area Business Woman Season 2000 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - San Francisco Classical Voice May 28, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - May 3, 1999 New Music Reading (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Concert Press clippings April 3, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - February 1999 Clippings (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - December 1999 Clippings (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - San Jose Mercury News 1/26/1997 Mediocre Text weakens drama of excerpts (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - SF Chronicle 1/26/1999 Opera pieces sit uneasily together (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - SJ Mercury News 1/17/1999 Engendering music (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - January 1999 Clippings (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Contra Costa Times 4/5/1999 WP Gives Rousing Performance (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Ann Krinitsky Conductor's award (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - SF Chronicle 12/12/1998 Second-rate tribute to a first lady (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - SJ Mercury News 1/17/1999 Engendering Music (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - San Francisco Classical Voice 12/10/1998 Chen Yi's stunning gift (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Symphony Magazine Apo/Jean Stapleton/Eleanor Roosevelt (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Apo Hsu ('99) Asian Trip review (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Apo Hsu Press (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - SF Examiner 11/16/1998 Music by women put to test (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - SF Focus Hot List 11/1998 Hear them roar (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - International Arts Manager Magazine 1/1999 Ladies first (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - SF Chronicle Datebook NEA gives $1.4 million locally (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - 8-9/1998 Clippings about 1998/1999 Season (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Misc. Clippings 7/1998 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Press Clippings 6/1998 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - SF Bay Times 6/25/1998 Conductor project (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Misc. Press Clippings about Music in the Making July 1998 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - San Jose Mercury 6/17/1998 "NWCI" (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - SF Chronicle 6/17/1998 NWCI (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Alameda Times 5/4/1998 Magnificent season ending for WP (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - The Times San Mateo County 2/6/1998 Female creativity is theme (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - SF Chronicle 5/4/1998 Women's Orchestra shows range (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Press clippings 5/1998 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - SF Business Times 4/3 - 9/1998 Orchestra blows its horn for sponsors (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Press/Newspaper clippings 3/1998 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Misc. mentions in press Spring 1998 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Allen's Press Clippings (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - 7/7/1993: SF Chronicle;Chen Yi/R. Staup. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - 2001 Press (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Alameda Daily Review 1999-2000 (Box 23)
  - Sacramento Gazette (2000) Apo Directs Youth Symphony (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - West County Times 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Tri-Valley Herald 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - The Times 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Star Tribune Article (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - San Ramone Valley Times 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - San Jose Mercury News 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - San Francisco Independent 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - San Francisco Downtown 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - SF Examiner-Chronicle 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - SF Chronicle 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - SF Arts Monthly 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Reporter 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Press Democrat 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Oakland Tribune 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Ms. Magazine 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Daily Review 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Contra Costa Times 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Bay View 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Bay area Reporter 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Bay Area Business Woman 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Chicago Tribune 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Alameda Times Star 2000-01 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - T.V. Guide 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Nov. 24th Press Clippings (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - SF Weekly (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Misc. Press: 1992-93 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1994 Press (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - 1998 Press (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - West County Times 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Wall Street Journal 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Valley Times 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - 2oth Century Music (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Tri-Valley Herald (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - The Times 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Santa Clara Mercury News 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - San Ramon Valley Times 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - San Mateo Co. Times (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - San Mateo Times 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - San Jose Mercury News 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - SF Frontiers 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - SF Weekly 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - SF Chronicle 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - SF Examiner-Chronicle 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - SF Classicle Voice 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - SF Arts Monthly (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - SF Business Times (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Sacramento Bee 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Richmond Post 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Reporter 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Press Democrat 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Oakland Tribune 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Neue Press 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Marina Times (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Marin Independent 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Key 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Express 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Daily Review 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Contra Costa Times 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Commuter Times 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - Chico News and review 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - Berkeley Tri-City Post 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 47)
  - Bay Area Reporter 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - Bay Area Business Woman 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - Asian Week 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - San Francisco Examiner/Chronicle (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Symphony 1982 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Symphony 1984 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Symphony 1985 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Symphony 1989 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Symphony Magazine 1988 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - 11/16/1987 Chronicle (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Chronicle Pink section 11/8/1987 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Examiner 2/8/1988 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Chronicle 5/2/1988 Vivian Fine Concert (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Pittsburgh Press 11/30/1984 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Unmarked Magazine article (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - SF Focus May 1986 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - 10/27/1986 Chronicle (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Ovation 12/1986 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - San Francisco Magazine 11/1987 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Symphony Magazine article 11/1988 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Tribune 2/11/1989 (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Chronicle 2/11/1989 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Examiner 2/11/1989 "Stellar Cellist" (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - San Jose Mercury News 5/2/1989 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Chronicle 5/2/1989 "Women's Philharmonic New Works" (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Stereo Review Feb 1993 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - May 6 1995 Cancelled Concert Press Clips (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - May 23 1995 Benefit Concert (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - March 11, 1995 Chamber Players Press Clips (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Chronicle "Women's Orchestra" March 1995 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - 3/11/1995 SF Chronicle Review (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - US Air Magazine 7/1995 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Chronicle "Glimpse of Sublime" Jan. 1995 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Reviews of 1/28/1995 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Reviews of 10/8/1994 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - JoAnn Falletta Interview Denver Post 3/1994 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Alameda Times Star 9/1/1994 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Critical Response 8/1994 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - San Jose Mercury News 2/28/1994 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - The Oakland Tribune 2/1/1994 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Misc 2/1994 Latina Reviews (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - SF Chronicle 1/31/1994 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Chron 11/20/1993 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Oct. 2, 1993 Reviews Jewish Concert (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Westways 9/1993 "Small Sclae Orchestra" (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - 7/15/1993 Staup Announcement (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Yerba Buena Season (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Bay Times-Vic. Bond 4/1993 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Performing Arts 4/1993 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Bay Area Reporter(BAR)- Women Aloud 4/1993 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - SF Chronicle--Bond Review 4/1993 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Children's Concert 3/1993 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - San Mercury News Feb 6 Concert (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Symphony Magazine Jan-Feb 1993 Lili Boulanger Award (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Bay Times 2/6 Concert (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - SF Bay Times Ching Chang Concert Jan. 14 1993 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Abram's Swan Song--SF Chronicle 5/1993 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Bay Times 5/1993 Miriam Resigns (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - E.Bay Express 5/14/1993 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Evening of Music Oakland Tribune 5/1993 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Examiner Oct. 1992 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Chronicle 11/16/1992 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - San Jose Mercury 10/5/1992 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - SF Examiner 10/2/1992 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Chronicle 5/1992 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Contra Costa Times 10/2/1992 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - SF Arts Monthly--October (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - Modesto Bee 10/25 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - SF Chronicle 10/5/1992 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Examiner 5/1992 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Washington Post 1/13/1992 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - McCall's 7/1990 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - NYT 7/25/1993 Recording (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - American Record Guide Record review (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Critical Response 6/1993 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Reno-Gazette Journal 3/7/1993 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Stereo Review Rec. Review 1993 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Koch Review-Gramaphone 2/1993 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Milwaukee Journal Rec. Review (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Fanfare Rec. Review 2/1993 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - American Record Review 1993 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Time 1/18/1993 Record Review (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - 2nd Rec. Review Sun Journal 12/20/1992 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Rec. Review Seattle weekly 12/1992 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Sun Journal 12/6/1992 2nd Rec. Review (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Orlando Senitinel Rec. Review (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Star Ledger, Newark Rec. Review 11/13/1992 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Arizona Republic Rec. Review, 11/20/1992 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - 10/29/1992 Denver Post 2nd Recording (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Womens Philharmonic's Vibrant New Disc (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - 10/29/1992 Bay Area Reporter 2nd Rec. (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - American Record Guide Sept/Oct 1992 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - 10/31/1992 JoAnn on T.V. (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Oakland Tribune Magazine 1992 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Ms. Magazine May/June 1991 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Examiner Pink Section 9/30/1990 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Pittsburgh Post Gazette (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Examiner 1990 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Examiner 4/20/1990 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - East Bay Express 3/1990 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - San Jose Mercury News 3/5/1990 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - CD Reviews 6/1993 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Sunday Republican 2/25/1990 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Newark Star-Ledger 2/23/1990 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - SF Bay Guardian 2/14/1990 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Chronicle 2/11/1990 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - SF Sentinel 2/9/1990 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Chronicle 2/5/1990 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - San Jose Mercury News 2/5/1990 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Examiner 2/5/1990 "So So Material" (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Examiner 2/2/1990 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - New Directions for Women Jan/Feb 1990 "Yes Mendelssohn Was a Woman" (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Center Voice 1/1990 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Musical America 11/1989 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Republican 10/29/1989 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - SF Weekly 10/25/1989 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Chronicle 10/23/1989 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Alameda Times Star 1999-00 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Key 10/29/1989 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - L.A. Times 9/19/1989 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - L.A. Times (editorial) 9/19/89 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - L.A. Times 9/10/1989 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - L.A. Times 9/18/1989 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - SF Chronicle 7/28/1989 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - SF Chronicle 6/2/1989 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - East Bay Express (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - L.A. Times/ASOL Concert 6/26/1989 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - 3/1995 Music Alive Educational Feature (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Chen Yi CD Release 5/5/1997 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Critical Response #2 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - May 13, 2001 Press Release (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Press (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Misc. Press (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Misc. Press (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - 1981-82 Misc. Press/Reviews (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - 1982 Misc. Press/Reviews (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - 1983 Misc. Press/Reviews (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - 1984 Misc. Press/Reviews (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - 1985 Misc. Press/Reviews (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - 1986 Misc. Press/Reviews (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - 1987 Misc. Press/Reviews (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - 1988 Misc. Press/Reviews (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - 1989 Misc. Press/Reviews (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - 1990 Misc. Press/Reviews (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - 1990-1991 press (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - 1991 Misc. Press/Reviews (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - 1993 Misc. Press/Reviews (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - 1992 Misc. Press/Reviews (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - 1994 Misc. Press/Reviews (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - 1996 misc.press list updates (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - 1997-1998 Misc. press (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Recent Reviews 1/1999 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - 1999 Press (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Misc. Press 1999 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Notes and Newspapers (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - March 3, 2004: press clippings (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Misc. Press 2001 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - San Francisco Classical Voice (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Noteworthy (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles Times Feb. 7 1997: Vienna Philharmonic protest (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Art News (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Long Beach Press (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - SF Arts Monthly (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Old Articles (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Symphony Mag. (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Misc. International Publications (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Press: 12th season (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Concert Press Release, Feb. 26, 2000 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - 2000 Season press release (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Florence Price press release and correspondence (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Misc. concert and donor brochures (Box 153, Folder 10)
- Series VII: Tours
  Tours
  This includes venues performed at, lodging and transportation logisitcs, for all non-Bay Area performances of the Women's Philharmonic.
  - General Orch. Info (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - CSU Long Beach (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - CSU-Long Beach (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - ODC/Larsen/McFerrin Spring 1993 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - May 22, 1994 Sacramento Concert (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - 1993-94: Israel/Jewish Concert 10/2/1993 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - 1993-94 season: General (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - 1993-94: American Concert 1/29/1994 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - 1993-94: N.Europe/British Concert 11/20/1993 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - 5/8/1993 Oakland Symphony Chorus Emily Hsieh (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Tour-Mill Valley (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Tour-Mill Valley (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Tour-Monterey (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Mountain View-Tour (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Tour-CSU Northridge (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - CSU Sacramento Tour (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - CSU Sacramento Tour (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - UC Santa Barbara Tour (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - UC Santa Cruz Tour (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Tour-San Diego (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Tour-Santa Rosa (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Kennedy Center 1/12/1992 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Kennedy Center 1/12/1992 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Tour November 18-20 1994 Program booklet (Box 18, Folder 11)